<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GuideTourApp</string>
    <string name="town_name">Zakopane</string>
    <string name="country">Poland</string>
    <string name="start">Start the tour</string>
    <string name="title_activity_background">BackgroundActivity</string>
    <!-- Category name for the nature category [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>

    <!-- Category name for the entertainment category [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_entertainment">Entertainment</string>

    <!-- Category name for the restaurants category [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Category name for the hotels category [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>

    <!-- Category nature items -->
    <string name="czarny_staw">Czarny Staw Pod Rysami</string>
    <string name="granaty">Granaty</string>
    <string name="koscielec">Mały Kościelec</string>
    <string name="chocholowska">Polana Chochołowska</string>
    <string name="za_mnichem">Dolina za Mnichem</string>
    <string name="rysy">Rysy</string>
    <string name="trzydniowianski">Trzydniowiański Wierch</string>
    <string name="piec_stawow">Dolina Pięciu Stawów</string>
    <string name="czerwone">Czerwone Wierchy</string>
    <string name="morskie">Morskie Oko</string>
     <string name="TPN">Tatrzański Park Narodowy</string>

    <!-- Category entertainment items -->
    <string name="trekking">Trekking</string>
    <string name="salt">SPA</string>
    <string name="ski">Ski or Snowboard</string>
    <string name="photos">Photography</string>
    <string name="bike">Bike</string>
    <string name="therms">Therms</string>
    <string name="climbing">Climbing</string>
    <string name="disco">Disco</string>
    <string name="maze">Maze</string>
    <string name="wildlife">Watching wildlife</string>
    <string name="spa">Art&amp;Spa Hotel, Zakopane</string>
    <string name="Lipki">Ski lift Lipki</string>
    <string name="Bukowina">Bukowina Tatrzańska</string>
    <string name="Kolorowa">Kolorowa, Zakopane</string>
    <string name="labirynt">Piłusudskiego 38, Zakopane</string>

    <!-- Category hotels items -->
    <string name="Aries">Aries Hotel &amp; Spa</string>
    <string name="Art">Art &amp; Spa</string>
    <string name="Tatra">Tatra Chalet</string>
    <string name="villa">Villa Miodula</string>
    <string name="gorska">Górska Osada</string>
    <string name="harenda">Osada Harenda</string>
    <string name="stamary">Grand Hotel Stamary</string>
    <string name="nosalowy">Grand Hotel Nosalowy Dwór</string>
    <string name="nosalowy_dwa">Rezydencja II Nosalowy Dwór</string>
    <string name="owca">Biała Owca</string>
    <string name="aries">Zaruskiego 5, Zakopane</string>
    <string name="art">Kościuszki 18, Zakopane</string>
    <string name="tatra">Bogdańskiego 5, Zakopane</string>
    <string name="miodula">Mocarni 17, Kościelisko</string>
    <string name="osada">Kośne Hamry, Poronin</string>
    <string name="Harenda">Harenda 28A, Zakopane</string>
    <string name="Stamary">Kościuszki 19, Zakopane</string>
    <string name="Nosalowy">Balzera 21D, Zakopane</string>
    <string name="Owca">Bogdańskiego 8, Zakopane</string>

    <!-- Category restaurants items -->
    <string name="czarci">Czarci Jar</string>
    <string name="kasza">Dobra Kasza Nasza</string>
    <string name="dworek">Góralski dworek</string>
    <string name="obrochtowka">Obrochtówka</string>
    <string name="adamo">Adamo</string>
    <string name="cristina">Cristina Ristorante</string>
    <string name="namaste">Namaste</string>
    <string name="pstrąg">Pstrąg Górski</string>
    <string name="casa">Casa mia</string>
    <string name="bakowo">Bakowo Zohylina Niznio</string>
    <string name="Polish">Polish cuisine</string>
    <string name="Italian">Italian cuisine</string>
    <string name="groats">Groats in a thousand ways</string>
    <string name="Indian">Indian cuisine</string>
    <string name="fish">Fresh fish</string>
    <string name="Mediterranean">Mediterranean cuisine, polish cuisine, vegetarian, vegan</string>
    <string name="Veg">Polish cuisine, vegetarian</string>

    <!-- Category nature descriptions -->
    <string name="czarny">Surrounded by the highest peaks in Poland, watches the sun only for a few months a year,
        at best only for a few hours a day. The water is reaching the bottom after 76 meters here and has an unusual,
        aquamarine color which contrasts wonderfully with the dark mountain walls. A gentle path snakes along
        the shore, which after several hundred meters of approach leads into the world of rock climbing to
        the highest point in the country. This is how it is here. Czarny Staw near Rysy.</string>
    <string name="granat">Grenades are three: Extreme, Intermediate and Zadnia,
        and each of them offers a slightly different landscape, but one combines them:
        the panorama has an extremely high mountain, full of horror and majesty character.
        Relatively high altitude (over 2200 m) allows you to admire the extensive panorama
        of the Tatra Mountains, which only on the southern Slovak side is limited by
        the high walls of Kozi Wierch.</string>
    <string name="kosciel">Kościelec is called the Polish Matterhorn, and it\'s best to photograph from
        Little Kościelec. This nearby and extremely attractive place is a mine of motifs, with one leading
        accent - the Kościelec pyramid. Even the entrance to the Karb Pass area allows you to feel the high
        mountain climate.</string>
    <string name="chochol">A gentle slope with 14 wooden shacks, over which you can see Wołowiec
        and Kominiarski Wierch, is one of the most charming places outside the peak parts of the Tatras.
        A special charm is gained after the season, or early in the morning, when there are no people and
        it is covered with mists backlit by the morning sunrays.</string>
    <string name="mnich">The valley behind the Monk is probably one of the most underestimated nooks and
        crannies of the Polish High Tatras, whereas in the place where from the yellow-marked trail leading to
        Szpiglasowy Wierch reflects the red trail to the Chałubińskie Gate, there is the most spectacular
        viewpoint on the Mięguszowieckie Peaks and their surroundings. Like this, they do not look from any
        other place accessible by the trail.</string>
    <string name="rys">Rysy is a unique mountain for many reasons. The most distant peak of the Polish Tatras,
        the highest available trail in the entire Tatra Mountains, also the highest peak of Poland (2499 m above sea
        level), and the panorama is unparalleled in the entire Carpathians. Thanks to a great location, on nice
        days the views reach a hundred kilometers. From Rysy, you can also see all important Tatra peaks, both on
        the Polish and Slovak side.</string>
    <string name="trzyd">One look from Trzydniowiański Wierch allows you to get to know almost the whole band.
        From here you can see not only the closest area from Kominiarski Wierch through Bystra, Starorobociański,
        Jakubina, Wołowiec, to Bobrowiec, but also Czerwone Wierchy, Giewont, Rysy, Mięguszowiecki Szczyt and
        Krivan.</string>
    <string name="piec">Dolina Pięciu Stawów is considered one of the most beautiful in Poland.
        On the blue trail in the Świstowa Czuba district, it is worth removing the camera from the case,
        because we have in front of us one of the best views of this valley. Of particular interest is the
        moment when shining panes of three lakes emerge from behind the Stawian Walls, surrounded by low peaks.</string>
    <string name="wierchy">Czerwone Wierchy is a mountain range consisting of four peaks, located between
        the races of the High Tatras, and limestone uplands of the Western Tatras. These hills are almost
        entirely covered with an unusual species of grass, which in the autumn begins to take a reddish color.
        The Czerwone Wierchy peaks illuminated by the setting sun appear then phenomenally.</string>
    <string name="morskie_oko">Famous in Poland and abroad Morskie Oko is the largest lake located in the
        Polish Tatras. This is one of the few lakes where fish, in particular trout, are found naturally.
        Breathtaking views and three red hiking trails that can be combined into one are just some of the
        attractions. On the route of trails leading to Morskie Oko you can see Wodogrzmoty Mickiewicza,
        a beautiful mountain waterfall.</string>

    <!-- Category restaurants descriptions -->
    <string name="czart">A tavern away from Krupówki, but it is worth spending a kilometer of walking.
        The decor is charming, regional. Highlander live music. Regional dishes exquisite: dumplings, moskal, ribs.
        Everything fresh, exquisitely served, large portions - will satisfy everyone.</string>
    <string name="kasz">Dishes are not expensive here (the cost of a meal is around PLN 20), and the size of
        the dishes served is large. The place is also friendly for vegans and vegetarians, and you can order
        half portions. You can also eat local delicacies (eg kwaśnica) as well as the standards of Polish
        cuisine (eg tomato soup). Many people recommend pearl barley with chicken and olives, as well as beef.</string>
    <string name="dwor">Menu created so that every gourmet will find something for themselves. The dishes are
        inspired by traditional Polish and regional cuisine.</string>
    <string name="obroch">A place with a homely atmosphere and delicious food. The cozy inn.
        Interesting also because of the television program "Kitchen revolutions".</string>
    <string name="adam">Excellent food. Light, aromatic and nicely served. Good coffee. The decor is very pleasant.</string>
    <string name="cristi">Pizzas served in the premises and very well evaluated by customers are prepared
        by a native Sicilian. In addition to them, typical Italian appetizers and seafood are served in Cristina.
        The best Tiramisu in town.</string>
    <string name="namas">If you\'ve always dreamed of eating like an Indian at home, you\'ve come to such a place.
        Please note, this is not a typical restaurant, there are only two tables in the middle, the menu
        is probably changing from the availability of products, but most importantly the food is delicious,
        cooked in front of your eyes.</string>
    <string name="pstr">A cult place. Being in Zakopane you have to come and eat trout - the choice is huge.
        A climatic place for both quick lunch and long dinners.</string>
    <string name="cas">According to customers, dishes here are not only tasty, but also beautifully served.
        A lot of people recommend white borscht and duck, as well as fish (for example, trout steak or
        salmon with black rice and orange sauce). There are also options for vegans and vegetarians.</string>
    <string name="bak">The soups are a hit - especially kwaśnica - for which you will pay about 10 zlotys.
        Eat here also tasty fish or mutton with additives at a price of about 20-30 PLN per person.</string>

    <!-- Category entertainment descriptions -->
    <string name="trek">The Tatra National Park is full of wonderful hiking trails, difficult
        and easy, short and long. All of them abound in breathtaking views.</string>
    <string name="sal">Zakopane, for tourists tired of mountain trips, offers rest in numerous,
        luxuriously equipped spa centers.</string>
    <string name="snow">There are several ski lifts around Zakopane. Perfect skiing conditions can
        be found both by professionals and amateurs.</string>
    <string name="photo">The Tatra National Park is a paradise for photographers. Thanks to
        the variability of the capricious Tatra weather, you can snap interesting photos without
        ending even in popular places. But there is still much to discover in Polish Tatras.</string>
    <string name="cycle">The Tatra National Park offers many wonderful bicycle paths.</string>
    <string name="therm">Surrounded by the National Park, you can relax in the thermal pools.
        Water extracted from the depth of 2.4 km from the north-west slope of the Wysoki Wierch mountain is
        warm, so you can enjoy the bath even in winter. The water park offers many attractions, such as a
        jacuzzi, massage, saunas and much more.</string>
    <string name="climb">Mountain climbing in Zakopane is an attraction dedicated to
        mountain enthusiasts and enthusiasts of active recreation. Certainly, those who have
        already tried their hand at climbing the mountain rocks admit that it is accompanied by an
        unforgettable adrenaline crowned with the joy of the summit. Mountain climbing is not only an
        amazing experience, but also breathtaking views and mountain landscapes that can be admired from high rocks.</string>
    <string name="club">In the evenings, Zakopane offers discos and dancing parties,
        some with live musics. In the summer season the commune organizes many concerts.</string>
    <string name="lab">The snow maze in Zakopane is great fun for families. Fortunately,
        the guards help out the lost tourists ...</string>
    <string name="wild">Just kidding! It\'s dangerous...</string>

    <!-- Category hotels descriptions -->
    <string name="Arie">When arranging and furnishing all rooms and suites, care was taken for their
        functionality and elegant style. Hand-decorated ceilings, mosaic wallpapers, and charming Zakopane
        views make the stay at Hotel Aries remain in the memory of the guests for a long time.</string>
    <string name="Ar">Hotel ART &amp; SPA is a four-star hotel located in the very center of Zakopane.
        Unique interiors and professional service guarantee a good rest in the mountains. The hotel offers
        spacious and comfortably equipped rooms, a modern Spa &amp; Wellness area, air-conditioned conference rooms,
        a restaurant serving European cuisine and a cozy café.</string>
    <string name="Tatr">Zakopiański Tatra Chalet is located close to Księży forest, Strążyska valley and the
        picturesque route "Droga pod Reglami". The center of Zakopane is just a 20-minute walk away.
        A perfect place for a romantic trip or family vacation. The relax zone with a sauna and a covered
        outdoor jacuzzi will also contribute to the rest of the body and soul.</string>
    <string name="vill">Villa Miodula, with panoramic views of the Tatra Mountains, is located
        on the southern slope of Gubałówka, close to the cable car and
        the ski lift. It offers traditionally furnished rooms and apartments. Villa Miodula was designed
        in a style typical of Zakopane architecture from the turn of the 19th and 20th centuries. Guests
        can relax by the fireplace or in the relaxation room.</string>
    <string name="gorsk">Accommodation in design wooden houses in a traditional
        style with modern elements, a fireplace and a private terrace.</string>
    <string name="harend">Osada Harenda is located in Zakopane, right next to the Harenda ski center,
        where there is an ice rink, ski lifts, chair lift and ski slopes. The chalet has a balcony,
        2 bedrooms and a living room with a fireplace. The living room is connected to the dining
        room and kitchenette. The cottage has 2 bathrooms.</string>
    <string name="stamar">Grand Hotel Stamary is located in Zakopane and offers elegantly equipped rooms,
        a spa, a wellness center and a swimming pool.</string>
    <string name="nosalow">Hotel Nosalowy Dwór is located in a quiet part of Zakopane, at the foot of the
        Nosal Mountain. The rooms are elegantly furnished in a classic style. They all have a private
        bathroom with a bath or shower. Guests of the Nosalowy Dwór have access to a spa and wellness
        center with a hot tub and a sauna.</string>
    <string name="nosalowy_dw">Rezydencja II Nosalowy Dwór is located in Zakopane. It offers a spa center,
        a ski storage room, a sauna, a fitness center and a restaurant. Rooms include a private bathroom
        fitted with a bath or shower. Ski equipment and bicycles can be rented on site. The area is very
        popular among skiing enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="owc">The White Sheep is a place that was created in harmony with the Podhale landscape,
        and at the same time a modern place, providing full comfort of rest. Willa Biała Owca is located at
        the foot of the Tatra Mountains right next to Droga pod Reglami and the entrance to the Strążyska Valley.
        Amazing views that extend beyond the windows will satisfy the most demanding Guests. The interiors
        of the White Sheep are a combination of modern design and elements of the highlander style.</string>







</resources>
